How did it go
For project communication, please submit materials through the Su Group, the Lu Group and
the bank's official tripartite process
In addition
Mr. Fu is not accepting private meetings for now
Fu Chenzhou is really putting on airs now
What is it
Brother Chengze
The Su family has changed too
Mom told me to apologize to my sister again
Dad isn't taking my side anymore either
This is not the time to talk about this
Do you also think it's all my fault
The Gu Group's projects are at high risk now
I don't have time to deal with your emotions
You weren't like this before
It's not that Gu Chengze isn't gentle
It's just that when I lose my value
he stops being gentle
Mengyao, is the food to your liking
It's delicious, thank you, Grandpa
Good, good
Eat more if you like it
He didn't like talking even as a kid
When someone gave him candy
he would keep it without eating it